John Mathew

6362968644 <u>anaghav.athreya@gmail.com</u>

Summary

Innovative Web Designer with 15+ years of experience in web designing, adaptation, and maintenance. Seeking to use extensive knowledge and background in front- and back-end web development to advance

Skills -

JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, React JS,PHP Node JS, Angular JS, MongoDB, AWS, Java, Python, SASS, Bootstrap, Jquery, C

Education

Stan University, Stanford CA

September 2017 – Present

- B.E. in Computer Science with focus in Web designing
- GPA: CS 9.87 Teaching: Intro to Web designing (PHP, Javascript)

The University of Texas

August 2011 - May 2015

- Dual major: B.C.A in Computer Science,
- GPA: CS 4.0 , Overall 3.88

Experience

Koi Industries, Pasadena, CA

September 2014 – Present

Web Developer

- Lead weekly Javascript workshops, fostering cross-functional programming ease and efficacy
- Implemented cross-platform browser plugins, improving overall website responsiveness and functionality and used HTML5, CSS3 and BOOTSTRAP.

JStar Technologies, Pasadena, CA

July 2012 – August 2014

Web Designer

- Employed mastery of front-end languages (Javascript, CSS3, HTML5) in collaboration with in-house web designers to create user-oriented visuals and features, increasing site traffic by 2,000 visitors per month
- Initiated and maintained compliance with BOOTSTRAP framework and Angular JS to enhance front end